Muh Roby Setiawan

Passionate Software Developer specializing in front-end web and mobile development

0812-7306-7776 robysetiawan2409@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/muh-roby-setiawan https://robysetiawan.vercel.app

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a seasoned Full Stack Web and Mobile Developer with over 6 years of experience in delivering exceptional digital solutions. My expertise spans a wide range of technologies including HTML/CSS, JavaScript, PHP, TypeScript, and frameworks such as React, Next.js, and Nuxt.js for web development, while for mobile development, I specialize in Flutter, React Native, and native iOS development. I have a proven track record of developing user-friendly websites and mobile applications that meet and exceed client expectations. I am committed to continuous learning and innovation in the everevolving field of technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - Oxy Creative / Jakarta - Jan 2021 - Mar 2024

- Developed a Private Swift Framework for SDK creation, iOS applications using UIKit and SwiftUI, and plugins for Flutter and React Native. And develop app for client, and app demo for private frameworks
- Successfully published apps on the App Store and plugins on CocoaPods.
- Created comprehensive documentation for plugins and SDKs.
- Utilized smart design techniques to optimize SaaS systems for efficiency and scalability.

MOBILE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER-IOS - PT. Djelas Tanda Tangan Bersama / Jakarta - Jun 2021 - Feb 2024

- Part of OXY Creative's Outsource Team.
- Developed mobile applications using flutter, and nuxt.js and collaborate with API services team.
- Orchestrated the seamless migration of services to new technology stacks.
- Orchestrated the design and implementation of databases for optimal performance and seamless functionality.
- Executed ongoing maintenance tasks with precision and efficiency, ensuring the highest standards of quality and user satisfaction.

WEB LARAVEL DEVELOPER - PT Kreasi Arduo Indonesia / Tangerang - Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

- Conducting proactive maintenance initiatives and seamlessly integrating new features into applications to enhance functionality and user experience
- Skillfully designing robust databases and translating intricate application requirements into efficient and scalable solutions..
- Maintaining existing menus on the admin dashboard.
- Adding new sections to the homepage and resolving bugs.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - PT. DHD Mitra Indotama / Palembang - Jan 2020 - Sep 2020

- Developed the backend (REST API) and front-end website, including the admin side, for a startup mobile app using Codelgniter.
- Created mobile applications using Flutter for the startup app.
- Implemented robust and scalable solutions to meet the app's requirements.
- Ensured seamless integration between the frontend and backend systems for optimal performance.
- Collaborated with the team to deliver high-quality software within the project timelines.
- Contributed to the design and architecture of the app to ensure its scalability and maintainability.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY BINA DARMA- Palembang – Sep 2016 - Jul 2019

Associate degree in Information Management

SKILLS

Language Skills

Framework Skills

Typescript, JavaScript, Php, Dart, Swift

Flutter, React native, Swift, React.js, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Laravel, Codelgniter

Languages

Bilingual in Indonesia and English.